Finding Aid for Minority Student Services (University of Michigan) publications, 1972-1986
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Minority Student Services (University of Michigan) publications 1972-1986
University of Michigan. Minority Student Services.
0.2 linear feet
2009031 Bimu 2
Office of Minority Student Services (MSS) was established in 1977 as successor to the Office of Special Services to meet the diverse needs of minority students and to promote the cultural diversity represented across the University. Name changed to Office of Multi-Ethnic Student Affairs in 1995. Includes miscellaneous brochures, directories, newsletters, and manuals.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
ACQUISITON NO.
Periodic additions to the records expected.
The Vice President and Chief Financial Officer records are open for research except for certain records restricted by statute or university policy. Restricted material includes personnel-related files, including search, review, promotion, and tenure files; student educational records; client/patient records; and records of executive officers of the university.
The RECORD GROUP record group includes restricted material in the following categories:
Personnel Related Records -- Boxes X_X
Student Academic Records -- Boxes X-X
Patient/Client Records -- Boxes X-X
Eecutive Officer Records -- Boxes X-X
In 1972, The Office of Special Services and Programs was a central area for communities of color at the University of Michigan, with a staff of advocates that served a variety of ethnic constituencies. In 1977, the Office of Minority Student Services (MSS) was created to meet the diverse needs of minority students and to promote the cultural diversity represented across the University. By 1995, the office changed its name to Multi-Ethnic Student Affairs, and included the Trotter Multicultural Center.
The Minority Student Services publications consist of miscellaneous brochures, directories, newsletters, and manuals.
Subjects:
University of Michigan. Minority Student Services.; University of Michigan. Community Services.; University of Michigan. Minority Counseling and Information.; Minorities at Michigan.
Genre Terms:
Brochures.; Directories.; Manuals.; Newsletters.
- Publications
  - Brochures, 1978-1986 (Box 1)
  - Directories
    - Minority Directory, 1981/82, 1989-1991, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Manuals
    - Minorities at Michigan, 1974-1980 (Box 1)
    - Profiles in Black, Red, and Brown (A Guide for Minority Students), 1972-1973 (Box 1)
  - Newsletters
    - Minority Student Services Newsletter, 1985-1990 (Box 1)
    - [Newsletter], 1980-1981 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous